Guide to the Bonnie Leslie Indonesian slide collection, 1975-1978.
Leslie, Bonnie Indonesian slide collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Bonnie Leslie Indonesian slide collection,1975-1978.
8432
Leslie, Bonnie.
.4 cubic foot.
Slides
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Collection consists of 35mm slides created by Bonnie Leslie during her time in northern Sumatra from 1975 to 1978.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Collection consists of 35mm slides created by Bonnie Leslie during her time in northern Sumatra from 1975 to 1978. They document weddings, funerals, and everyday life of local ethnic groups. Many photographs focus on the Toba Bataks, but images of the Simalungan, Karo, and various other ethnic groups are also included. Locations depicted are Aceh, Asahan, Bukit Tinggi, Hari Kamerdekaan, Jakarta, Jogjakarta, Kuala Lampur, Lake Toba, Marbun Pollung, Medan, Parapat Pasar, Pearata, Penang, Prambanan, Samosir, Seribudolok, Siantar, Si Langit, Sipipak, Sipirok, Tanjung Balai, Tarutung, and Toba.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Leslie, Bonnie.
Subjects:
Rites and ceremonies -- Indonesia.
Places:
Indonesia -- Social life and customs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Siantar, June 1975-April 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  First days in sumatra. Rice fields, churches, Toba choirs, friends.
- Parapat Pasar scenes, June 1975-December 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  View of Toba in Parapat. Sunset over Lake Toba
- Various sites including Pearata and Lake Toba, July 1975-January 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Hari Kemerdekaan, August 1975-August 1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Various images of agriculture and churches, August 1975-December 1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Karo Batak Village, September 1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Sipipak and Marbun Pollung, October 1975-April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Two funerals, October-November 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Asahan, December 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Siantar Pasar, December 1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Simalungan villagers church, April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Trip to Sipirok for teaching seminar, April 1976 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Near Sibolga, Lyman-Munson grave, Taratung churches, Tetti Hutapea's Home, miscellaneous
- Simalungan Village trip, April-May 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Rubber plantation Goodyear, May 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Kuala Lampur, June 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  Malacca and Malasia
- Penang, June-July 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Christian and Muslim weddings, July 1976-March 1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Trip to Nainggolan, Samosir with students, August 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Toba village, September 1976 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Various sites including Bagan Harbor and Tarutung, September-November 1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Toba and Samosir, October 1976 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Bonnie's trip to Aceh, October-November 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  Nommensen student activities
- Seribudolok, November 1976 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Seribudolok water project, March 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Bukit Tinggi, April 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Overview of B.T, M.T., women at Dessa, Ngari, Lake Maninjau, Sados, D on horse, Minang houses.
- Tanjung Balai and Medan, April 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bukit Tinggi, April-May 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Lake Singkarak, street scenes, Lembus. Trip Home, S.S. in Parapat, funeral.
- Jakarta, May 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Jakarta Bogor, May 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Jakarta flight market, May 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Jakarta Prambanan, May 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Prambanan, May 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Seribudolok, October 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Student retreat
- Si Langit retreat, Indonesia, October 1977 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Jogjakarta paintings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Sumatra farewell, January 1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)